(Amy:)You were still hot,
but more like a
"why'd that hot girl
cut off all her hair?" hot.
(Penny:)You liked my
short hair, right?
(Leonard:)Yeah... I loved it.
(Leonard:)Love you, love the hair, would
love to change the subject.
(Penny:)Seriously, none of you liked it?
(Bernadette:)I thought it was brave.
(Bernadette:)Does that count as liking it?
(Penny:)You know, how come
nobody's talking about
(Penny:)Howard's dopey haircut?
(Bernadette:)I think he looks cute.
(Howard:)And I think
you're cute.
(Raj:)I think you're both cute.
(Penny:)I think I hate all of you nerds.
(Sheldon:)Sorry I'm moving slowly.
(Leonard:)Oh, I don't mind.
(Leonard:)If you pull a butterscotch
out of your pocket,
(Leonard:)it would be like I'm
walking with my grandma.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no.